2026 at this point?
And I know there's
a lot in your
research, but is there
a best idea or
narrative? Just quickly, if
you could. Well, so
the top three stocks
in our flagship are
Tesla. We think it
has miles to go.
We do take profits
from time to time,
but it could break
out here in a
big way as more
and more analysts do
their homework on robotaxis.
Mm. Crispr Therapeutics has
moved into the second
position. That company is
curing sickle cell disease
and beta thalassemia and
has its eyes set
on not just rare
diseases, but curing the
bad cholesterol problem, especially
for those who have
hereditary issues in that
realm. That could be
an enormous market, and
I don't think anyone
is doing the modeling
work there the way
we are. I love
it. All right. Hopefully,